# JACK GUILLORY

567-455-1320 | New Iberia, LA | jack.p.guillory@gmail.com

# **WEB DESIGNER**

Computer Science graduate and geek adept at creating web applications based on client requirements. Accustomed to writing code, updating websites, designing layouts, editing content, and making adjustments based on client and user feedback. An expert in design, content management, multi-media programming, creativity and problem solving.

**Software:** Git, Wordpress, Google Suite, Adobe Creative Cloud, Slack **Coding:** Javascript, HTML5, CSS, Python, C, C++, Perl, Unix Bash Shell

Knowledge: Git Hub, Scrum

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **GUILLORY DESIGNS** | New Iberia, LA

2018 to Present

#### Freelance Editor & Game Developer

- Worked with and managed cross-functional teams on audio, video, and game projects including: *How Not To* (game), *Xinyu's Chinese Quiz* (game), *Rocket Runback* (trailer), *Windmill's Wake* (trailer and web series), etc.
- Debugged Javascript code for RPG Maker MV plugins.
- Completed 130 video projects.

#### BRISTOW GROUP | New Iberia, LA

2019 to 04/2020

#### **Flight Follower**

- Developed Outlook macros in Visual Basic for Applications to speed up workflow.
- Communicated calmly and efficiently in time-sensitive situations regarding the status and location of up to 130 helicopters and fixed wing aircraft per shift.
- Relayed information between a variety of customers, coworkers, and businesses.

#### **CRIT HIT ENTERTAINMENT** | New Iberia, LA

2017 to 2018

#### **Content Manager & Video Editor**

- Created and edited videos, podcasts, motion graphics, banners, logos, and thumbnails.
- Released over 75 collaborative video projects on a consistent schedule.

# NASA / SOUTHWESTERN OKLAHOMA STATE UNIVERSITY | Weatherford, OK

Summer 2016

# Intern

- Performed legacy code maintenance in Perl, Python and C, and created Python scripts.
- Automated MAPSS install and setup for new workstations.
- Utilized Unix Bash shell for a variety of tasks.

# AUXILIUM GAMING: CHINESE DUNGEON & FIGHTER | Weatherford, OK

2013 to 2015

### **Senior Online Support Representative**

- Aggregated information for help desk manuals and edited guides for a better user experience.
- Performed knowledge management for organization.

#### **EDUCATION & AWARDS**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science | Southwestern Oklahoma State University | Weatherford, OK | 2016

**2<sup>nd</sup> Place Winner** – Univ. of Tulsa High Performance Computing Competition | 2016 **Top 10** – Dungeon Fighter Online Official Art Festival | 2016